YUSUF Aishah Damilola

07034807554 <u>aaeshayousuf@gmail.com</u>

Gender: Female
Nationality: Nigerian

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY ___

Front-end development trainee and a specialist in landscape design, architecture and management with proficiency in horticultural and related skills. Areas of expertise include architectural ideating, ornamental conceptualization, research, communication skills, leadership and project management, while being resourceful in agricultural practices. Efficient in team work, hard work and productivity.

SKILLS _____

- Front-end Development
- Landscape Design
- Landscape Management
- Project Management
- Communication
- Leadership and Teamwork

PERSONAL QUALITIES _____

- A critical thinker with positive attitudes and behaviour.
- Excellent communication skills.
- Proficient in the use of computers.
- Self-motivated, dedicated and target oriented.
- Inclination for research and innovation.

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATION _____

Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta.

- B. Agric, Horticulture

Silver Child Model College, Ijoko, Ogun State

- West African Examination Council (WAEC) 2012

WORK HISTORY _____

Front-end development trainee, Zuri International

2021 till date

${\bf Horticulturist/Landscape\ designer,\ Deluxe\ Bloom\ Gardens}$

2020

2019

Duties:

- Draw up landscape plans for spaces ranging from professional to casual.
- Assigned work and duties during field work.
- Estimates work-hour requirements to plant, wet, and prepare work schedule.
- Supervised landscape work for various work and residential places in Lagos and Abuja.

Horticulturist/Landscape designer, Adline's Outdoor (Parks & Recreation), Abuja **National Youth Service Corps (NYSC)**2019 - 2020 **Duties:**

- Assigned work and duties during field work.
- Estimates work-hour requirements to plant, wet, and prepare work schedule.
- Supervised landscape work for a residential apartment in Minna, Niger State.
- Trained an intern in horticultural techniques such as transplanting and weeding, identification of ornamental plants.
- Provided moodboard for proposed design projects.
- Prepared and submitted written and oral reports of project works .

| OTHER ADMINISTRATIVE EXPERIENCE | |
|---|----------------|
| Member, Horticulture Students' Association (HORTSSO) -Worked under various committees between years 2013 and 2018 | 2013 |
| Public Relation Officer, Muslim Students' Society of Nigeria, FUNAAB | 2015 |
| Member, Islamic World of Talents and Creative Minds (ISWOT) | 2016 till date |
| CERTIFICATIONS | |
| Participant, MFB (MyFarmbase Africa) Global Agriculture Development | |
| Program (2-weeks online course), Cohort 3.0 | 2020 |
| • Participant, Environmental Education Outcomes (25-hour Professional | |
| development online course), Cornell University | 2020 |
| • Participant, Urban Environmental Education, (20-hour Professional | |
| development online course), Cornell University | 2019 |
| • Participant, Floriculture, Centre for Entrepreneurial Training, FUNAAB | 2016 |
| • Participant, Landscape Design, Shodex Beautification Landmark Ltd, Lag | gos. 2014 |
| COMPUTING SKILLS | |
| Real-time Landscape Design | |

- Basic Desktop Applications
- Sketch-up
- Adobe Premier Pro

HOBBIES/ EXTRA SKILLS _____

- Writing: Quotes
- Travelling

REFEREES ____

To be provided upon request.